World Harvest Church
====================

World Harvest Church
====================

LOVE GOD. LOVE PEOPLE.

Close [Home](https://whc.life/) [Columbus Campus](https://whc.life/columbus) [Elkhart Campus](https://www.whcelkhart.com/) [Online Campus](https://whc.life/online) [Russian Harvest](https://russianharvestchurch.com/) [Give](https://whc.life/give)

[Columbus Campus  
Ohio](https://whc.life/columbus) [Elkhart Campus  
Indiana](http://www.whcelkhart.com/) [Online Campus  
Live Streaming](https://whc.life/online)

Privacy Policy
--------------

World Harvest Church, Inc. ("WHC") is a Christian, nonprofit organization committed to excellence, integrity, and your privacy. Our mission is to earn and build your trust and confidence by promoting and upholding the highest standards concerning principles of disclosure and informed consent. This Privacy Policy is provided to inform you of the ways we gather and use information on WHC websites, their subdomains, affiliated domains, or other WHC controlled Internet presences, as well as any WHC owned and controlled application, whether hosted or available on Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Google, or any other third party domain, and governs data collection and usage (collectively "Websites" or “Website”). For a list of WHC websites, visit [http://whc.life/whc-websites](http://whc.life/whc-websites). This Privacy Policy does not apply to any website "linked" to these Websites, and WHC is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such other websites. By using the WHC Websites, you signify your acceptance of the terms of this privacy policy.  

**Information Collection**  
  
Please be aware that WHC is committed to upholding the highest level of confidentiality and security for those who choose to visit our Websites. The types of information collected by WHC on these Websites fall under one of two categories: Anonymous or Personal.  

**Anonymous Information**  
  
Anonymous information cannot be traced back to a specific individual. WHC’s web servers automatically record the IP address (the general location where the user is logged) of each visitor to these Websites and tracks how many people visit our Websites. There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by WHC. This information can include your operating system and version, browser type and features, domain names, access times, and referring website addresses.  
  
WHC uses this type of anonymous information to administer the WHC Websites more effectively, personalize the Websites for you, and gain general information about the backgrounds and sources of visitors, for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding how the WHC Websites are used. WHC uses such identifiable information collected to continually improve the content of its Websites and to offer its visitors products and services that best meet their preferences, needs, or desires. In so using this information, WHC is able to refine their Websites and enhance the benefits they offer.  
  
When possible, WHC collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your zip code, age, gender, preferences, interests, and favorites. This data is handled by a third party.  
  
WHC keeps track of the Websites and pages our visitors use within WHC in order to determine which of WHC's services are most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within WHC to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area and for no other purpose.  
  
**Location Information**  
  
Upon visiting the RodParsley.com web site, you may be alerted by your modern web browser or mobile device that our website would like to know your location. Please be assured your physical location is not tied to your user account or any other personally identifiable information and is not stored on our servers (as of Tuesday, October 14, 2014). It is only polled to serve you by finding scheduled ministry tour dates and locations to inform you when Pastor Parsley will be in your area, and only during that visit to our website.  
  
**Personal Information**  
  
Personal information identifies who you are. You can use the WHC Websites without divulging any personally identifiable information, including your e-mail address. The Websites do not collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address, or telephone number, except when you specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis as a result of a prompt on the Website.  
  
WHC does collect and uses your personal information, when you provide it, to operate the WHC Websites and deliver the services you have requested. WHC also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from WHC and its affiliates. WHC may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.  
  
Credit card numbers may also be collected when online transactions occur through our Websites. Following is a list of ways that WHC collects personal information from these Websites:  

**Online Requests for Information**  
  
When you request information online from our Websites, we ask for certain information in order to process your request. The information may include, but is not limited to, your name, postal address, phone number, email address, and other demographic information that we may use to send you additional literature about WHC and its events and resources.  

**Online Registration of Our Partners**  
  
When an individual registers a user account with WHC, certain information is collected to allow us to provide you with the highest degree of excellent service. The information collected in our online registration may include, but is not limited to, your name, postal address, phone number, email address, and other demographic information. Please be aware that we value your privacy, and your registration information is protected by password for your privacy and security.  

**Online Transactions**  
  
When you desire to purchase resources from our Websites or make a donation, certain information is necessary to allow us to ship your order to you as quickly and efficiently as possible or process your online donation. The information collected in an online transaction may include, but is not limited to, your name, credit card information, bank account information, postal address, phone number, email address, and/or other demographic information. Because your privacy is of the utmost importance to us, we have taken steps to ensure that online transactions through our Website take place via encrypted secure servers. All the information you include and submit with your order or request for online donation is passed through our encrypted secure servers which meet or exceed requirements handed down by the Payment Card Industry for encryption and security as validated by our PCI Compliant certification.  

**Cookies**  
  
Cookies are small data files that can be placed on your hard drive by websites that you visit. The only personal information that a cookie can contain is information that you provide to us personally. WHC uses cookies to gather and store personal information that is collected when online transactions occur on our Websites, as well as preferences (used for secure login) of registered users visiting our Websites to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can be read only by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.  
  
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize WHC’s Websites or register with WHC’s Websites or services, a cookie helps WHC recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This allows WHC to deliver messages and material more specific to your needs and to simplify the process of recording your personal information, such as your billing address, shipping address, and so on. When you return to the same WHC Website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved so you can easily use WHC’s features that you customized.  
  
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the many valuable interactive features of WHC's services or Websites you visit.  

**Security of Your Personal Information**  
  
WHC makes every effort to secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. WHC protects the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.  

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
  
In the ordinary course of its operations, WHC does not rent, sell, lease, or share its customer lists to third parties. There are occasions in which WHC might undertake one of these activities, subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. WHC may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In addition, WHC may retain the services of a third party vendor to assist it as it attempts to determine whether an individual desires to be retained on WHC's mailing list or whether that individual might be better served by another service or entity. In addition, WHC may share data with trusted partners to help it perform statistical analysis, send you e-mail or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.  
  
WHC does not disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.  
  
WHC may share personal information about you in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal processes, or to establish and/or exercise our legal rights.  

**Children's Policy**  
  
If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian before you use or email WHC Websites, request that WHC send any information to you, or purchase any resources on WHC Websites.  

**Opt-Out or Unsubscribe Policy**  
  
To opt out of or unsubscribe from receiving emails or standard mail solicitations or other forms of contact from World Harvest Church, Inc. including Breakthrough with Rod Parsley or Bridge of Hope, send an email to info@whc.life with “Opt-Out” in the subject line, or send a letter to: World Harvest Church, P.O. Box 200, Columbus, OH 43216. You must include your full name, mailing address and e-mail address. If we are able to locate your contact information based on the information you provide us, it will be removed from active lists in our databases and mailing lists.  

**Editing Your Account Information**  
  
If you determine that our information about you is inaccurate or has changed, you may modify that information by:

> Letter  
>   
> World Harvest Church  
> PO Box 200  
> Columbus, OH 43216  
>   
> Email: info@whc.life  
> Phone: (800) 637-2288

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**  
  
WHC reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy without advance notice. WHC welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that WHC has not adhered to this statement, please contact WHC at info@whc.life. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.  

**Contact Us**  
  
If you have any further questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please call us at 1-800-637-2288, or email us at info@whc.life.  
  
Last changed: 01/06/2016

Copyright © 2024 World Harvest Church All rights reserved.

**WHC Columbus**  
4595 Gender Road, Columbus, Ohio  
  
**WHC Elkhart**  
1610 S. Nappanee St, Elkhart, Indiana  

[](javascript:fncTakeoverClose(); "Return to WHC.LIFE")

[No, thanks.  Return to what I was doing.](javascript:fncTakeoverClose();)
